The Steal is a thriller, comedy film directed by John Hay.
A young American computer hackeress is hired by a liberal British lawyer to right the
wrong done to a third world country by a London investment company.
Even the expertise of her building inspector sidekick can
not prevent a surprising development though.
Kim, played by Helen Slater.
Cliff, played by Alfred Molina.
Lord Childwell, played by Peter Bowles.
Sir Wilmot, played by Dinsdale Landen.
Jeremiah, played by Heathcote Williams.
Wimborne, played by Stephen Fry.
The Steal is a 1995 British comedy thriller film directed by John Hay and
starring Alfred Molina, Helen Slater and Peter Bowles.
The film was released by Warner Bros.
in the United Kingdom on six screens on 5 May 1995.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.